<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Author Bio &amp; Press Site for Thomas Dylan Daniel</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Author Bio &amp; Press Site for Thomas Dylan Daniel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:37:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Formal Dialectics Is Coming Out Soon!</title>
      <link>/fdcover.png</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:37:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fdcover.png</guid>
      <description>Click for a quick preview of the cover of the book. More news to come!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Further From Home is in Stores!</title>
      <link>/ffhonshelf.jpg</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 01:31:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ffhonshelf.jpg</guid>
      <description>Further From Home is available from Book People and Half Price Books in Austin, both on Lamar. Thanks to these wonderful booksellers for getting local authors out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is IPFS?</title>
      <link>/posts/what-is-ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 22:16:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-is-ipfs/</guid>
      <description>You may be wondering what on earth IPFS is. I’ve been very excited to use this new technology to bring you this site, and I’ve been posting about it everywhere. Here’s a quick breakdown of just what IPFS is, what it means, and what may happen in the near future as a result of this breathtaking technical accomplishment.

What is IPFS?
IPFS is an acronym which stands for “Interplanetary File System” and is literally designed to make information transportable between different planets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Decentralized Internet</title>
      <link>/posts/welcome-to-the-decentralized-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 21:22:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcome-to-the-decentralized-internet/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Decentralized Internet.
In this life, there are few things more certain than change. This site, for example, used to be a Wordpress site hosted by a company with a server. It is still the primary website of an analytic philosopher, but everything else about it has&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;changed, recently.
Today, in fact.
Now, instead of being hosted by a single entity, this site is hosted by a &amp;ldquo;swarm&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;peers&amp;rdquo; (put in scare-quotes just to emphasized the novelty of the two concepts).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>