<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Author Bio &amp; Press Site for Thomas Dylan Daniel</title>
    <link>/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Author Bio &amp; Press Site for Thomas Dylan Daniel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 20:16:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Download The Need for a Standard Index of Vehicular Pollution Intensity in the United States</title>
      <link>/ogel2015-article022.pdf</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 20:16:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ogel2015-article022.pdf</guid>
      <description>In late 2015, the International Journal of Oil, Gas &amp;amp; Energy Law published this essay.
Abstract:
The Environmental Protection Agency is tasked with providing a guide to automobile consumers which indexes the smog output of a particular car and compares that car to others. The ratings system used is complicated and accounts for zero emissions vehicles (ZEVs) as well as large trucks and everything in between. Unfortunately, this convoluted structure leads to a complexity which is simply not practical from the standpoint of the end user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download The Lexicultural Propagation of Concepts</title>
      <link>/the-lexicultural-propagation-of-concepts.pdf</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 19:55:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-lexicultural-propagation-of-concepts.pdf</guid>
      <description>In late 2014, I presented this essay to the Southern California Philosophy Conference. It was accepted and published in a book edited by Brian Thomas, available on Amazon. ISBN: 978-1443880428</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Brief Lives: Pierre Hadot</title>
      <link>/pierre-hadot-1922-2010--issue-113--philosophy-now.pdf</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 08:13:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pierre-hadot-1922-2010--issue-113--philosophy-now.pdf</guid>
      <description>Here is an article I wrote for Philosophy Now back in 2015. It deals with the late French philosopher, Pierre Hadot. He&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite philosophers, and I&amp;rsquo;m attaching a .PDF so you can have a look! The article appeared in Philosophy Now&amp;rsquo;s April/May 2016 issue (no. 113).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>